onehourtranslation.com 2011-12-05

# Privacy Policy - One Hour Translation

1\. One Hour Translation uses industry standard efforts, such as firewalls, to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. However, as all security measures are subject to possible circumvention, we cannot and do not provide any guarantees regarding the effectiveness of the security we employ or our ability to prevent third parties, acting unlawfully, from obtaining information that you provide to us. The Owner cannot and does not guarantee that any personally identifiable information provided to us will not become public under any circumstances. You should appreciate that all information submitted on the Website might potentially be publicly accessible. The Owner cannot ensure that your identity, telephone number, work or home address and other personal identifying or contact information will not be discovered by other Users of the Website. Important and private information should be protected by you. The Owner encourages all Users to maintain a pseudonymous identity when using the Services provided by One Hour Translation or any other public aspects of the Website.   
2\. We use your personal information to provide the Services we offer: Your profile, language skills and User name are displayed in order to facilitate User interaction and for purposes of our matching Services. With the exception of inviting friends and certain notifications, a User email address is not shared or displayed.   
3\. Members may communicate between themselves using One Hour Translation translation project pages, without disclosing their email addresses, PayPal User names or any other method of communication, including phone, ICQ, AIM, MSN Messenger, Google Talk, etc.   
4\. To facilitate searching and finding Service Providers on the Website, One Hour Translation allows Members to submit their translation requests using public projects boards. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in the course of using the Services provided by One Hour Translation and/or participating in any of the public pages available via the Website becomes public information; accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.   
5\. To facilitate searching and finding Service Buyers on the Website, One Hour Translation allows Members to search for translation projects using public projects boards. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in the course of using the Services provided by One Hour Translation and/or participating in any of the public pages available via the Website becomes public information; accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.   
6\. The Owner may archive information, including personal information, you provide in the course of using our Services and any other aspects of the One Hour Translation Website. We store that information on servers that are controlled by us or by third parties who have agreed to comply with our commitments made under this Privacy Policy and with whom we have a contractual relationship. Archived information will not ordinarily be erased unless and until your entire account with One Hour Translation is deleted, and even then we may retain some or all of your information on back-up files; provided, however, we assume no obligation or guarantee to archive any information and do not warrant that any archived information will later be made available to you.   
7\. We may use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve the Services we offer.   
8\. We will not share your information with third parties, with the exception of the following: 

a. We may provide information to Service Providers to help us bring you the Services we offer. Our Service Providers may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities.

b. We may be required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law or to protect our interests or property. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

c. If the Ownership of all or substantially all of the One Hour Translation business or assets were to change, your User information would likely be transferred to the new Owner(s).

d. We may share with, or disclose or sell to, third parties aggregated information which does not reference individually identifiable Users.

9\. If you do not want to receive promotional email from One Hour Translation, please submit a request by emailing us at [info@onehourtranslation.com](mailto:info@onehourtranslation.com). We will make reasonable efforts to implement any choice you make as soon as possible; provided, however, The Owner reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to the One Hour Translation Services, such as service announcements and administrative messages without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.   
10\. This Website may contain links to other websites. The Owner is not responsible for the Terms and Conditions including the privacy practices of other Websites. We encourage our Users to be aware when they leave our Website and to read the statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information.   
11\. One Hour Translation Users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account. For technical reasons, any modifications or deletions which you request may take a short period of time to take effect. If you change or delete any of your personal information, One Hour Translation will remove the old or deleted information from public view; however, as noted in Section 6 above, we may keep such information archived indefinitely.
